Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
What?
Yeah, Let's get on with it.
Yeah,
Yes.
Calm.
Yeah.
Get off
the doctor.
No!
Rock!
Rock, Rock.
Mhm!
Back to your business.
Mhm.
Mm.
No.
Really?
Yeah.
Nutritious.
Mhm.
My focus is picking up some kind of signal.
Maybe I could scan it
this whole last.
Yeah.
And
Well,
okay, they're heading back.
Yeah,
Trust me.
Yes.
Oh.
Mm hmm.
Mhm.
Just stay out of their way for now.
Yeah.
Can stop tensing up.
Six.
Okay.
Yeah.
E can still get the upper hand.
Okay,
Okay.
Yeah.
Mark?
Shall we say
Yeah.
Okay.
They're skinny.
I thought they go on forever
from a place.
Yeah.
Mhm.
Yes.
Okay,
that's
yeah.
What?
Yeah, okay.
Yeah,
right.
A cauldron.
There's gotta be a way in somehow.
Mhm.
I wonder what's down here.
Uh huh.
Yeah, Some kind of liquid flowing through that pipe.
Mhm.
Yeah,
She
okay.
Looks like I'm not the first to look for a way in what a waste
things will keep.
They were curious to, but I'm better prepared.
E hope it's enough.
What?
This is
right.
He wants to
Yeah.
Okay.
That's circular device.
What does it dio?
Looks like things are going my way.
Happy
without brushing sound again?
Uh huh.
Oh,
okay.
Need to find a way through that shell.
Yeah.
School.
This is
Yeah.
Protection.
Okay.
What?
Have you given any of the hunt?
Thank you.
Yes.
What makes this a little easier.
All right.
Uh huh.
You know,
right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Mr.
Restaurants.
Stop.
We always
Yeah,
right.
yeah.
Get
six.
Oh,
perfect.
Free.
All right.
That should get me through.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
Police.
Yeah, Yeah,
yeah.
All right.
Mhm
When
you get a little bit, Have this time?
Uh huh.
Okay.
Save these for the trail.
Yeah,
easier when I was a kid
saving these for the trail.
Your car?
Yeah.
Yeah,
yeah.
Subject.
It's
yes.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Yeah,
right.
Your dad, The others haven't noticed
for me.
Thank you
for machines.
Collective plays from the wilds.
And it all flows here like love to heart.
So the culture runs on life itself.
Yeah,
Yeah.
Come on.
Me,
Right?
Yeah.
Okay.
You think?
Look behind.
Yeah.
Yeah,
hold off.
Just
Yeah,
e need to be closer to use that.
Oh,
thank you.
Come on.
Sure.
Yeah.
Yourself?
Yeah,
I'm safe for three years.
Oh,
yeah,
That was my chance.
Yeah.
Low and quiet.
Does it?
Yeah.
Oh, thank you.
Please.
Yeah,
Yeah.
I'm
picture.
Yeah, Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
I'd have to pitch something.
Mhm.
Yes.
We have
access to resources.
Okay.
Yeah.
Yes.
Okay.
Just a moment.
Great.
You're alert
after leaving.
Just
Yeah.
Beautiful.
Course
you can
e have to leave something else behind.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Thank
thank you.
Yeah.
Okay.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah,
yeah,
I think.
Yeah,
sure.
yeah,
yeah.
It's yes.
Yeah.
Thank you.
That's where I need to go.
The belly of this giant beast.
Okay.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
This one.
Yeah.
Can't be too prepared.
Thanks for that.
That's where I need to go.
Can't carry more.
Yeah, Yeah,
yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Traffic.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Thank you.
Just to
thank you.
Okay.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Uh huh.
All right.
Yeah.
Forget.
Thank you.
Good morning.
Okay.
They're scaring for me.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Okay.
Well,
yeah,
Yeah.
Red light.
Thank you.
You left me.
That's exactly
right.
Yeah.
Tell me.
Yeah,
I think so.
Cool.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yes.
Yeah.
Get this.
Yes.
Yeah,
Yeah.
That's not
right here.
No.
Right here.
Right.
Moreover, yeah.
Killing supplies.
Lucky.
Okay.
Thank you.
This is about to get a lot of her.
The prosecution.
Oh, yeah.
This is
something.
Thank you.
Okay.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Pass the test.
Yeah.
All right.
Three.
Okay.
Mhm.
It was successful.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Okay,
that's it.
Well, machines, I can have a ride.
Do you think?
No.
Summary.
Active production.
Oversight Analysis.
Additive manufacturer type alert.
Intrusion Source.
External active countermeasure phase.
Shift alert.
Intrusion denied.
Alert intrusion Source.
External countermeasure.
Phase shift.
Breach firewall.
3706403 Reboot purge.
Successful intrusion denied.
E